[{"answer": "Well, it seems that the French aircraft that spotted this Libyan aircraft, and as far as we know the type of aircraft that's a trainer aircraft used for training pilots who are going to move on to fighter jets.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "What can you tell us about that?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "It seems to be having an impact around Misrata.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "And Nic, I mean, do you get a sense of the no-fly zone is actually having much of an impact on Gadhafi and his regime?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, I think it is the transition that the president talked about where our role diminishes somewhat, we're still very central in the planning.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "I mean, on the ground, militarily and politically, what difference does it really make?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, no someone is pretending that America is not involved.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "I mean, just looking at the way this has all been playing out, it seems to me that America is heavily involved but doesn't really want anyone to know that which seems to be a rather pointless exercise in terms of the PR here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, I have to disagree with you there.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "And dare I say it, leadership here?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, we're concerned, and we are involved to stop a massacre.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "So why should you be overly concerned?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, I think, first of all, our -- the objectives militarily have been clear from the beginning.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Are they in this or not really?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "First of all, I don't think we're withdrawing leadership on the diplomatic, on the political stage.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Does America then re-enter the fray?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, I think it has consistency in the sense that we see throughout the region that people are demanding both greater participation in their political life and also greater economic opportunities.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Where does this policy have consistency?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "OSNER: It's America's job to lead on human rights and democracy.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Is it really America's job to get involved in civil wars?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "You know, what it eventually will bring could easily be $100 to $150 million.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "John, is that an accurate assessment?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "And some of the jewels were actually from the duchess of Windsor's collection, weren't they?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Without question.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "And that makes her, John, I would imagine, one of the great private jewelry collectors of all time, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I think Elizabeth Taylor of the maximum of glamour in the world right now.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Was she Hollywood's queen in all senses including the tiaras and bangles?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to say, but perhaps the Krupp diamond which was -- she was almost never -- not wearing it.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "And John Block, what would be -- from your knowledge of the collection, the single most valuable piece that she owned?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "RINCE DIMITRI: Well, I think they went together.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Don't you think, if I put you on the spot, do you think she preferred her diamonds to her men?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "The only time she told me she ever bought jewelry for herself was at the Duchess of Windsor sale.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "And, John, if I could turn to you, I mean, did Elizabeth Taylor ever buy jewelry herself, or was it always just given to her by admiring men?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I didn't know her that well, but I think she liked to be remembered for her charitable works, for the -- for her totally generous personality.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "How would -- how would you imagine that she would like to be remembered knowing her as you did?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "From being a fan -- from what I heard from lots of people who knew her is that she was an incredibly kind person.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "And, Prince Dimitri, what would your memory of her be just from being a fan?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Piers, we have been getting aftershocks every single day since the March 11 earthquake and tsunami.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "What exactly is going on here?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "We understand they're in a stable condition.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Do we know what their condition is?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "This is a very big story at the moment here in Japan because contamination is spreading.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What's the latest advice there from the Health Ministry?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "And Jules, did you speak to her much about life in Japan?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "About 5:20 on Monday morning.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "And Jean, when did you get the terrible news that confirmed that she had died?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Did it ever cross your mind that something awful could happen?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What can you tell me about that?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Oh, she was loving and fun filled.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "How would you like people to remember your daughter?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "The only real things that I had going on in my mind were making sure that anyone who was injured, not just the congresswoman, but anyone who had been just in the immediate area got some treatment, and using whatever limited skills I had until someone who was better trained could come in.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What was going through your mind as you ran towards her?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "So, the congresswoman as well as others had been shot.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What did you actually do to Gabby Giffords?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Did you fear in that moment that she was probably going to die, given the injury she'd sustained?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "She was conscious, but she wasn't able to speak.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Did she say anything?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I think for people that don't know Congresswoman Giffords, it -- it's stupendous the amount of recovery that she's been able to make in such a short amount of time.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Can you quite believe that she is where she is now?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Still something that I'm not very comfortable with.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "How do you feel about being called a hero?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "No, I'm for marriage.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Are you against marriage?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110324pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Do you think you will get married?", "qSentId": 530}]